I'm sorry Meredith
I should have just made it
very black and white
when I was asked questions
I didn't go out and say that
I'm so sorry I'm so
so sorry so sorry
I'm truly
truly sorry but I feel like I'm being
the I'm sorry has to come with no condition
I'm sorry, I'm sorry Meredith
the last thing I would ever do
is hurt you
within every attempt
the person keeps stepping on their own toes
they're like but they're like
I would never
I could have said
I should have just said this or said that
and it's like the person can say
I apologize for saying what I said
for doing what I did and I
I was wrong for that and I apologize for it
a beautiful way that an apology can happen